ADANBIOJE, SAMUEL ANUOLUWAPO

4, Ayeni Layout, Ashipa Road, Odo-Ona Elewe, Orita-Challenge, Ibadan. | 08106930144; 09027775884 samueladanbioje@gmail.com

Summary

An exceptionally diligent and resourceful young graduate with the character mix required for excellence in chosen areas of work interest, particularly in pedagogy, customer relations management, digital marketing and banking sector.

Possess excellent communications and negotiation skills, with ability to maintain productive and mutually beneficial relationships across all levels of the organization, particularly with respect to actualizing organizational goals.

I am passionate about work, and very committed to delivering optimum quality services at all times. Also, I seek to constantly improve myself through good quality learning experiences and cognate professional exposures, thereby building an improving professional value.

Career Objectives

To work in an organized business environment with a good corporate culture, well-motivated staff team and a clear vision.

To work in a result oriented and challenging environment suffused with self-development opportunities, teamwork and commensurate reward while contributing the best of my abilities and quota to attain organizational objectives and achieve managerial goals and targets.

Education

The Polytechnic Ibadan

Higher National Diploma, Graduated October 2017

Federal Polytechnic Offa

Ordinary National Diploma, Graduated April 2014

Employment History

SEAP Microfinance Bank Ltd.

Teller, August 2019 - Present

Provides account services to customers by receiving deposits and loan payment. Cashing checks and issuing of saving withdrawals. Answering questions in person; referring to other bank services.

Kajola Middle High School, Ajaba, Ila-orangun. (NYSC)

Teaching Staff, September 2018 - July 2019

Responsibilities:

• Plan, develop and teach academic subjects to students in secondary school. • Worked as subordinate teaching staff in charge of extracurricular development of students in secondary school. • Monitored and evaluated the students learning process, and make required recommendations to engender improvements.

Independent National Electoral Commission (INEC)

Assistant Presiding Officer (APO I), INEC Ambassador, Presiding Officer (PO), September 2018 - March 2019

Responsibilities:

· Worked with range of teams to manage complex electoral processes. · Sensitized the electorates on voters' education and conducts during election. · Presided over the distribution and collection of Permanent Voters Card (PVC).

Lead Radio 106.3, Ibadan.

Graduate Intern, May 2018 - August 2018

Responsibilities:

· Developed and uploaded online information and promotional materials. · Effectively managed social media presence pages.

Samskillz Laundromat

Administrative Manager, November 2016 - August 2018

Responsibilities:

• Prepared and managed staff and general operations schedules. • Managed customer relationship which includes communications duties, trouble- shooting to ensure their satisfaction and promotion of the organization. • Directed non-merchandising department of business, such as Advertising, promotion and purchasing.

Professional Skills

Excellent Team-work and critical thinking and analysis ability. Self-motivated, targets oriented and very adaptable. Excellent presentation, writing and communication skills. Proactive and diligence. Customer Service.

Computer/I.T Skills

- Proficiency in MS office suite
- Digital marketing/Content creation.
- Proficiency in online information mining and management.

Professional Certification

2019: Certified Digital Marketing Expertise

Google Digital Skills for Africa.

2019: ACIPM (In View)

2019: Management Strategies for People and Resources

Young African Leaders Initiative.

Professional Development: Conferences, Training and Publication

2016: Apostle Awode Business Symposium; The Polytechnic Ibadan.

2017: Participant; JCI James Fadairo Speech Competition, Lagos.

2017: Junior Chamber International Leadership Training Retreat, Oyo.

Adanbioje, S.A.: A study on the use of the social media by public relations practitioners in Ibadan. (Unpublished HND research)

Leadreship Roles

• Protocol Officer: Junior Chambers International (JCI), The Polytechnic Ibadan Chapter.

Interests

• Reading, Travelling and Professional networking.

References

Available upon Request